

MUJEEBUL RAHIMAN SYED

UX Designer

July 9, 1999

+91 72072 77738

rehamansyed979@gmail.com

Hyderabad, India

Skills









Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Teluqu
- Urdu

Hobbies & Interest

- Cricket
- Volleyball

Links and Credentials



<u>Linkedin</u>



<u>Instagram</u>



<u>Behance</u>

About

I am a skilled Interaction Designer with over 2 years of practical experience in the realm of UX design. My journey into UI/UX design began in my first organization, where I started as a fresher, despite my educational background in electrical engineering now a lifelong student of design.

Education

2017 - 2020

 Usha Rama College of Engineering And Technology , Vijayawada.

Bachelor of Electrical and Electronics Engineering

I graduated in September 2020 with a GPA of 6.69 in Electrical and Electronics Engineering.

2014 - 2017

 Usha Rama College of Engineering And Technology , Vijayawada.

Diploma in Electrical and Electronics Engineering

I Completed my Diploma in September 2020 with a Percentage of 73% in Electrical and Electronics Engineering.

Experience



Capgemini Technology Services India Limited

Senior Software Engineer UI UX Designer | Nov 2021 - present

Collaborated closely with senior designers and crossfunctional teams to understand requirements and translate them into visually stunning user interface designs.

- Created wireframes, prototypes, and visual mock-ups using Adobe XD, Illustrator, and Figma to effectively communicate design concepts.
- Leveraged illustration skills to craft captivating graphics and visual assets, enriching user engagement and reinforcing brand identity.
- Continuously iterated and enhanced designs to meet rigorous standards, resulting in heightened user satisfaction and garnering positive feedback.



Adwaitham Global IT Solutions Pvt. Ltd

Associate Analyst UX UI Designer | Sept 2020 - Nov 2021

Collaborated with cross-functional teams to create visually appealing and captivating designs for concept and production vehicles and related digital platforms.

- Designed user-centered interfaces using Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, and Figma resulting in improved user experience and increased customer satisfaction.
- Conducted trend reports on the latest UI/UX developments, emerging technologies, and techniques, providing valuable insights to the design team.
- Assisted in creating visual and interaction design, maintaining consistency with a cohesive style guide.